const List<Map<String, String>> beginnerQuestions = [
  {"question": "A fruit that is red", "answer": "apple"},
  {"question": "A vehicle with two wheels", "answer": "bicycle"},
  {"question": "A place where you can borrow books", "answer": "library"},
  {"question": "A device used to take photographs", "answer": "camera"},
  {"question": "A tool used for cutting grass", "answer": "mower"},
  {"question": "A container used to hold water", "answer": "bucket"},
  {"question": "A small, sweet food made with flour, eggs, and sugar", "answer": "cake"},
  {"question": "A device used for writing or drawing", "answer": "pencil"},
  {"question": "A place where you can buy and sell goods", "answer": "market"},
  {"question": "A small, round fruit often associated with pies", "answer": "cherry"},

];

const List<Map<String, String>> mediumQuestions = [
  {"question": "A reptile that moves slowly and has a shell", "answer": "turtle"},
  {"question": "A device used to play music", "answer": "stereo"},
  {"question": "A small, fast-running bird often associated with roadrunners", "answer": "ostrich"},
  {"question": "A mode of transportation on water with oars", "answer": "rowboat"},
  {"question": "A type of flower often associated with love and romance", "answer": "rose"},
  {"question": "A reptile often kept as a pet that can shed its tail", "answer": "gecko"},
  {"question": "A large bird of prey known for its sharp vision", "answer": "eagle"},
  {"question": "A mode of transportation on snow with long, flat boards", "answer": "snowboard"},
  {"question": "A tool used for cutting wood", "answer": "saw"},
  {"question": "A type of footwear with a flat sole and open top", "answer": "sandal"},
];

const List<Map<String, String>> expertQuestions = [
  {"question": "A celestial body that orbits the Earth", "answer": "moon"},
  {"question": "A unit of currency used in Japan", "answer": "yen"},
  {"question": "A large, flightless bird native to Australia", "answer": "emu"},
  {"question": "A type of evergreen tree often used as a Christmas tree", "answer": "pine"},
  {"question": "A small, nocturnal mammal known for its ability to fly", "answer": "bat"},
  {"question": "A large marine mammal often associated with the Arctic", "answer": "whale"},
  {"question": "A mode of transportation with two wheels powered by pedals", "answer": "bicycle"},
  {"question": "A small, venomous snake often found in deserts", "answer": "viper"},
  {"question": "A large, predatory fish known for its sharp teeth", "answer": "shark"},
  {"question": "A type of bird known for its distinctive call and colorful plumage", "answer": "parrot"},
];
